Viewers all over the world, whatever medium you are using to view us,
you are with us and we are with you.
This is the moment of salvation,
moment of healing,
moment of deliverance,
moment of breakthrough.
Hallelujah!
Remember at this moment, you have been forgiven of all your sin
and if the Son forgives you, you are delivered.
Say to yourself, "If the Son forgives me, I am delivered".
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself -
these are the instruments satan uses to connect us to himself.
Sickness, hardship, depression - whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself;
open your lips, by the power of restoration,
that good health that has been taken from you,
that promotion that has been taken from you,
your destined position that has been taken from you,
your destined marriage that has been taken from you -
be restored, in the name of Jesus!
By the power of resurrection, be restored, in the name of Jesus!
That good health that has been taken from you - be restored.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Promotion that has been taken from you - be restored.
I command the power of resurrection to restore you back.
Say, "Restore me back, in name of Jesus!"
Restore me back!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus!
You deserve good. You deserve excellent.
That good health that has been taken from you - be restored, by the power of resurrection!
Be restored, by the power of resurrection!
That promotion, that good career, that promotion - be restored, by the power of resurrection!
Open your lips.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Watch your screen.
There is confusion in the kingdom of darkness; right now, demons are...
Look at your screen right now and see what the people are vomiting out.
See what is happening - people are vomiting out poisonous substances
and demons are manifesting in the lives of people right now.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus!
The power of resurrection, restore you back.
Good promotion, your promotion, your destined promotion,
your destined career - be restored!
If you are enjoying your destined career, you will not complain.
Destined career, promotion, position -
by the power of resurrection, be restored in the name of Jesus!
Your destined marriage, promotion, position, good health -
be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips.
You satan, whatever you might have used to connect them -
be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen. You see people still vomiting out the poisonous substance in their system
or what they have eaten from the table of the enemy is what the Holy Spirit is flushing out right now.
Right now, begin to use your faith to place a demand on this anointing.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
That sickness in your body, that disease in your kidneys, liver, blood, blones, fluids, womb -
be cured!
Open your lips! Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Open your lips!
Viewers, open your lips!
By the power of resurrection, that good health that has been taken from you,
that promotion that has been taken from you,
your destined position that has been taken from you,
your destined marriage that has been taken from you,
your destined position that has been taken from you -
be restored, in the name of Jesus!
By the power of resurrection - be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Watch your screen.
People at the overflow section, you can see them right now under the influence of the Holy Spirit.
See what is happening.
They have vomited out poisonous substances in their system all over the church right now.
By the power of resurrection!
In the name of Jesus, I command that sickness - out.
Be healed!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen.
You can see clots of blood in what that person is vomiting out.
Open your lips.
You are going to be delivered - that is the joy of resurrection.
You need freedom, liberty - receive!
In the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Watch your screen and see what people are still vomiting out.
You are going to be restored into your destined promotion, position, marriage!
Say, "I am going to be restored to my destined position, in the name of Jesus!"
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Be restored!
In the name of Jesus Christ.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Confess your restoration.
Every dead thing,
every sick part, organ - be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Be restored, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Every sick organ - be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips. Begin to fire on.
Every sick organ, faculty, system - be it your organs, blood, kidneys, liver, bones, fluids, womb -
be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Right now, begin to disconnect your business from anything that has to do with demons, satan.
Disconnect your business from failure, backwardness.
Disconnect your marriage from backwardness, setback.
Disconnect your business from failure, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to disconnect your business.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Disconnect your business, from failure.
I disconnect my business from failure.
Every element that causes you pain - disconnect your business, life, career!
Right now, begin to disconnect your marriage from backwardness, failures, isolation, unforgiveness.
Begin to disconnect your business, yourself, your life, marriage, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, disconnect your health from affliction.
Wherever there is affliction hidden, wherever it is located -
disconnect yourself, disconnect your health.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah!
I want to rejoice with you.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I rejoice with you because Jesus has made you fit.
Jesus has made you whole.
I say, "I rejoice with you".
Hallelujah!
Give thanks to God.
Right now, remember your loved ones on the sickbed.
Jesus sent forth His Word, healed them and blessed them.
Right now, begin to send your word of healing, blessing, breakthrough to your loved ones.
Wherever your loved one is - right now prayer to your loved one.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus' mighty name we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen.]
Right now, your nation. Remember your nation in prayer.
Begin to cover your nation with the blood of Jesus.
Ask God's intervention.
God's intervention.
Open your lips.
Speak a word of deliverance, restoration.
Power of restoration - speak it to your country.
God's intervention.
In the name of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ' name.
Right now, those of us that have just known Jesus and those who want to rededicate themselves,
open your lips and say after me:
Lord Jesus, come into my heart, wash me with Your precious blood.
Make me a channel - a channel of shining light where there is darkness.
Make me a channel - a channel of love where there is hatred.
Make me a channel - a channel of humility where there is pride.
Make me a channel - a channel of obedience where there is disobedience.
Make me a channel - a channel of pardon where there is hurt, in Jesus Christ's name.
Thank You, Lord!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Don't forget the message today.
God does not want you to succeed and lose your kids to drugs.
He does not want you to succeed financially and lose your children to the world.
He does not want you to succeed financially and lose your kids to militants.
Think about that.
What does that mean to you?
Many of us are here today, we have succeeded; we are rich.
Talk of rich, we are rich but we have lost our children to drugs. militants, to the world.
You see them on the streets.
That is to show that if we don't look back
and see what we can do to restore these children, we may lose it all.
We may what?
[Lose it all.]
If we don't look back, back to those children,
and see how we can restore them, because we gave birth to them, we may do what?
[Lose it all.]
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
That is Easter blessing.
When you get back home, you see them and ask yourself,
"My son is a drug addict. Ah! Look at what this man of God said.
I have money, I have everything, I am a Christian but this man of God is telling me now
that if I don't restore this boy - because this is not the way God gave you,
God never gave you a drug addict, God never gave you a militant -
but you have to restore these children back -
if not, you may lose it all.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
That is, at the time we need this blessing, we are becoming old.
This is Easter blessing for you.
I am at your service.
This is a message - very big message.
You may not look at it as a very serious message.
Happy Easter but very, very serious message.
What this man of God is saying is a very serious message.
So let's pray. Father, we thank You.
I can hear the sound of joy in your career.
I can hear the sound of joy in your finances.
I can hear the sound of breakthrough in your business.
I can hear the sound of joy in your marital life.
Breakthrough!
In Jesus Christ's name.
Rejoice!
TT: Monica Asefa 06/09/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 29/09/2018